this, welcome to another video of a cobalt strike. So, I was loving on future futures
in a cobalt strike, that was we can load a custom modules in a cobalt strike if I you
held in a cobalt strike concept. So, you can see there are few commands. So, DLL, let's
take an example, elevate, spawn a section and elevate it like might be this can be used for
privilege escalation. And if you need to execute a program, you need to give the execute command
to execute a program on a target. And there is lot of lot of commands that has been available.
But if you want a custom of scripts, okay, like this. So, you can get it from Google
I can be able to download it in your own way. So, if you want to, if you want to create any new
commands like this, okay, commands like this mimic ads or no ports can. So, you can go ahead.
So, there is a name, there is a script called this Aggressor scripts. There was available
in the GitHub. So, here you can find lot of CNF files. So, if I go to the CNF file. So, this is the
program which our cobalt strike has been using. So, you can see Dicon to M pair. So, it will
automatically convert the cobalt stick to M pair Dicon. And many cards, every 30 minutes, 30
minutes, M and most DC sync attack you can do. And you can see a lot and lot of Aggressor script.
And the function of the Aggressor script will be listed here. So, if you go down, there is a
five other Aggressor repose. So, here you can find lot of other Aggressor scripts. Like,
you can able to, here you can see the autocaloger.ca. So, we know key loger is used to to record
the keys. When the user pressing any keys inside keys in the keyboard, it will be automatically
get recorded. So, if you can load the CNA easily, also we can other script scripts to lateral moment,
download screenshots, PowerShell, CNA, STTPC, and name. So, elevate kit we have for our privilege
installations. And here you can see AV query.CNA. So, it will list what are the antivirus software
will be present under the machine. And there is a EDRCNA. So, it will list all the EDRs,
which will be original. So, there is lot of options you can do. You need to, if you need to
load a custom script. So, the custom script loading the custom script will be pretty easy. Let
me teach you how to do that. So, let us download this in your machine. We will unzip the file.
First extract here. So, now, our script does present under the cell D. Let us get a server script.
Let me do extract here on more time.
Here it is. Here you can find all the CNA files as in load here. Just go to the cobalt
string, click on the cobalt string, script manager, load. So, you need to choose the path which
path you need to load. Let us select this. So, we will check the AV query.CNA. Let us load this.
Now, the AV query has been loaded. So, if I give the help here, now you can see the AV query
right. So, previously, there is no AV queries as in present in the first. But if you see now,
the AV query has been here. So, it will automatically sets one of the AVs here present on the machine.
So, we can easily do some enumeration in our target. Like finding out what other
antivirus has been installed and we can create a code based on that. Or, if you have a custom
payload that will bypass, make a fee, or be different or any antivirus program, you can
inject the program based on the AV query results. So, I was downloading some of the
useful scripts. Let me put the manager. So, you can load many customized payloads in us.
Sorry, customize the CNA files, the script files. So, based on your attack
button, you can download that. Okay? Let me download everything.
So, I will be loading what are the CNA files, which I am needing in a football slide. So,
if you have a football site, just load what are the things you want. If you want to develop
a custom payload, custom CNA files, say you can go ahead and do that. If you know the programming,
for the CNA file files and the structure,
so that's all. We'll hop off this video and we will continue our discussion in the next video.
See you guys, bye-bye.